PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm a 25 years old Art Director & Freelance Designer from Valladolid (Spain) currently based in Madrid. I love everything that has to do with Web design & development, Graphic design, Packaging, Industrial design and I feel a true devotion for typography.

I have 4 years of experience working as a freelance and working on an studio, but and I'm ready for visiting other countries & work for any design studio! I love working with people, specially if they have the same passion I have for what they do.

Why don't we work together? Go futher down to see whay I am the man you need to hire!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer/CoFounder



2019 - ongoing Phouston, Tx

Worked within teams of creative freelancers to build the backbone of professionally designed websites from the ground up, including coding websites (HTML, Javascript, JQuery and CSS), designing UX wireframes, and fixing sites bugs.

- •Created UX strategies, including mockups using Figma. •Transferred static HTML website to Wordpress.
- $\bullet\,\mbox{\sc Validated}$ completed sites, including testing and debugging of code.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites, including validating web forms and links.
- Collaborated and communicated with an international team through slack.

Web Developer - Freelancer



2019 - ongoing PHouston, Tx

Worked within teams of creative freelancers to build the backbone of professionally designed websites from the ground up, including coding websites (HTML, Javascript, JQuery and CSS), designing UX wireframes, and fixing sites bugs.

• Created UX strategies, including mockups using Figma.

- •Transferred static HTML website to Wordpress.
- Validated completed sites, including testing and debugging of code.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites, including validating web forms and links.
- Collaborated and communicated with an international team through slack

Full-stack Developer

🛅 2019 - ongoing \, Q Lagos, Nigeria

Worked within teams of creative freelancers to build the backbone of professionally designed websites from the ground up, including coding websites (HTML, Javascript, JQuery and CSS), designing UX wireframes, and fixing sites bugs.

- Created UX strategies, including mockups using Figma.
- •Transferred static HTML website to Wordpress
- Validated completed sites, including testing and debugging of code.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites, including validating web forms and links.
- Collaborated and communicated with an international team through slack.

EDUCATION

BS. in Computer Science

University of Houston

2010 - ongoing

Computer Science University of Houston

2010 - ongoing

RELEVANT COURSES

Data Structures React(Udemy)

Computer Organization React(Udemy)

RECOGNITIONS



Best Roku's App to connect People Hack Houston TSU 2018

SKILLS

Frontend



Backend





HOBBIES & INTERESTS











